CV

Miloš Živadinović

About me



Solutions engineer with more 8+ years of experience in different teams and roles. Focused on providing great pre/post/during sales experiences as a trusted advisor to the stakeholders. Experience in leading teams and planning business strategies. Holding an MSc and on the road to a PhD.

Passionate about solution engineering, technical management, AI/ML, blockchain and security. Technology agnostic, as well as able to learn new technologies quickly. Able to de-

sign and implement novel solutions to existing problems at hand, no matter the complexity.

My motto is: That which is above is like to that which is below, and that which is below is like to that which is above.

Contact

Phone: | +381 (0)69/11-27-001 Email: | mzdv@protonmail.com

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/milos-zivadinovic-16950b62/

Github: | https://github.com/mzdv

Work experience

Arija Nebeska

August 2022 - current Owner / Software Engineering Consultant https://arijanebeska.rs

Responsibilities: Business development and sales activities as a freelance consultant. Hiring of external specialists for demanding projects. Project management and development in a variety of technologies (Node.js, Cloud, React, Spring). Managed to help several companies with their stuck projects, increasing their revenue.

Oracle

January 2021 - current Senior Solutions Engineer https://oracle.com

Responsibilities: Sales, pre-sales and post-sales activities regarding Oracle Cloud Infrastructure (OCI) solutions. Tech lead for a team of two salespeople in Serbia. Sales and consulting support for team members in other countries. Deal evaluation, management and technical qualification. Proof of concept development, after-sales support and customer satisfaction management. One of advisors to bringing Oracle Cloud Region to Serbia. Helped increase cloud recurring revenue in Serbia 3x since start.

United.Cloud

September 2019 - January 2021 Senior Software Engineer / Team Lead https://united.cloud

Responsibilities: Team leader for two developers, one QA and one designer developing UWP Windows video streaming application. Scrum master for part of time. Communicating key information with stakeholders. High level solution development and research, acting as senior software engineer regarding C#, ASP.NET and UWP. Drop-in development roles with different teams. Optimized managerial process that allowed us to become top-performers. Scaled application from 5k to 15k users.

Ignis Potentia

June 2018 - September 2019 Owner / Blockchain Consultant https://ignispotentia.com

Responsibilities: Business development and sales activities as a freelance sales consultant focusing on blockchain. Lead two projects from initial design to completion as an external consultant. Hiring of frontend specialits and management. Experience in Hyperledger, Golang nad Python.

FIS | February 2018 - September 2019

Senior Software Engineer

https://fisglobal.com

Responsibilities: Worked in Strategy Enablement as a senior software engineer focusing on concurrent systems programming and software architecture. Managed to deploy a solution for programmatic API access to Front Arena's internal trade engine with on average 30% faster performance.

NCR | August 2016 - February 2018

Solutions Engineer

https://ncr.com

Responsibilities: Pre-sales and post-sales activites. Acted as one of key contact with customers and their tech teams. Developed multiple Proof of Concept for NCR's NDC line of ATMs based on Aptra Advance NDC. Managed to perform back to back integration between ATM fleets and Authentic transaction processing engine.

Education

PhD | 2022 - current

Faculty of Organizational Sciences, University of Belgrade

Information technologies

Research focus: Artificial neural networks

MSc | 2016 - 2017

Faculty of Organizational Sciences, University of Belgrade

Information technologies

Thesis: Management of cryptographic keys using blockchain technologies

BSc | 2012 - 2016

Faculty of Organizational Sciences, University of Belgrade

Information systems and technologies

Thesis: Usage of Kerberos authentication in distributed telemetry systems

Languages

Balkan languages | Native
English | Native
Hungarian | Advanced
German | Advanced
Slovakian | Beginner

Special skills

- Highly adaptable to different problems and environments
- People person with the ability to rapidly gauge reactions and situations
- Ability to choose best tool for the job without prejudice
- Background in cyber-security (red-team and blue-team)
- Experience and motivated in leading small teams (up to five persons)
- Competitive shooter (IPSC/USPSA, IDPA)